
Warning: Module "openssl" is already loaded in Unknown on line 0
��
Warning: Module "openssl" is already loaded in Unknown on line 0

STATEMENT OF WORKBetweenBILLIONS UNITED, a registered sole proprietorship firm  having its office at #35, 1st Floor, 24th Main,J.P.Nagar 7th Phase, Bangalore   560078 herein referred as Service Provider or the First PartyAnd ${organization_name} Having its registered address at Here in referred as the client or the second party SOW DETAILSSOW Number${sow_number}SOW Date${sow_date}MSA ReferenceMaster Service Agreement dated Between Billions United and ${msa_reference}Service ProviderBillions UnitedClient${organization_name}Client Contact Person${contact_person}Service Provider ContactBillions UnitedEffective Date of SOW${effective_date}Expiry / Delivery Date${expiry_delivery_date}SCOPE OF WORKPursuant to the Master Service Agreement referenced above, the Service Provider agrees to deliver the following services / database supply to the Client:#Service / DeliverableDescription / SpecificationsQuantity / Volume1Database Supply${target_segment}${database_quantity}2SMS Campaign (if applicable)Bulk SMS blasting using Service Provider's platform. ${sms_quantity}3WhatsApp Campaign (if applicable)WhatsApp broadcast messaging via approved business API. Template messages as approved by Meta. Client to provide content and creatives. Language: [English / Hindi / Regional].${whatsapp_quantity}4RCS Campaign (if applicable)Rich Communication Services messaging campaign. Includes rich cards, images, and CTAs. Content and branding assets to be supplied by Client. ${rcs_quantity}DATABASE SPECIFICATIONSData Fields Included${data_fields_included}Data Fields ExcludedPan, Aadhar, CIBILTarget Segment${target_segment}Target Geography${target_geography}Salary Band Filter${salary_band_filter}Industry / Sector Filter[All]Delivery FormatMS Excel (.xlsx) /  password protectedDelivery ModeEmailAuthorised Recipient Email${authorised_recipient_email}CHARGES AND PAYMENTDatabase Supply Charge${database_supply_charge}SMS Campaign Charge${sms_campaign_charge}WhatsApp Campaign Charge${whatsapp_campaign_charge}RCS Campaign Charge${rcs_campaign_charge}Total SOW Value${total_sow_value}GST${gst_amount}Payment TermsAdvance PaymentPayment Due DatePayment ModeNEFT / RTGS / UPI TDS Applicability(if applicable)PERMITTED PURPOSE AND USE RESTRICTIONSThe Client confirms that the Database and services under this SOW shall be used solely for the following Permitted Purpose, as defined in the MSA:Product / Service Being Marketed${product_service_marketed}Marketing Channel${marketing_channel}Marketing TeamClient's in-house team onlyPermitted Geography for Outreach${permitted_geography_outreach}USE RESTRICTIONS: The Client shall not resell, sub-licence, share, or redistribute the Database to any third party. Any such action shall constitute a material breach of the MSA and this SOW, triggering immediate termination and full indemnification obligations under MSA Clause 8.CLIENT RESPONSIBILITIES UNDER THIS SOWAs per Section 3 of the MSA SERVICE PROVIDER RESPONSIBILITIES UNDER THIS SOWAs per section 4 of the MSAINCORPORATION OF MSAThis SOW is subject to and governed by all terms and conditions of the Master Service Agreement between the Parties In the event of any conflict between the terms of this SOW and the MSA, the terms of the MSA shall prevail, except to the extent this SOW expressly overrides a specific MSA provision for the purposes of this engagementBoth the parties agree to the terms of this statement of work and signs below FOR BILLIONS UNITED(Service Provider)FOR ${organization_name}  (Client)86487024257000Signature: Name: Billions UnitedDate: ${client_date}Place: BangaloreSignature: ${client_signature}Name: ${contact_person}Date: ${client_date}Place: ${client_place}
